dojiggy.com 2018-10-14

# Privacy Statement | DoJiggy

## Information Collection and Use

The information we collect is: used for internal review and archived for historical comparison, used to improve the content of our web site, and never shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. It is not sold or shared in any way, unless disclosed here. We send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people:

  1. When we have your consent to share the information;
  2. When we need to share your information with third parties, such as banks and credit card processors, to provide the product or service you have requested;
  3. It is appropriate to comply with the law;
  4. It is necessary to enforce or apply the terms and conditions of our Terms of Use and other applicable agreements; or
  5. It is necessary to protect the rights, property, or safety of DoJiggy, our users, or others, which may include the exchange of information with other organizations for fraud protection and/or risk reduction.
  6. In the event that DoJiggy is acquired, customer account information may be one of the transferred assets.

This website uses cookies. Cookies set by our website can be read by our web server and may contain information provided by you, or certain limited information commonly provide by your network connection, such as IP number, type of browser, operating system, etc. This information is used only in connection with the purposes outlined here. Information about the general use of our website will be stored and reviewed. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.

Web site activity data is analyzed. This website uses web analytics software, to help us analyze how users use the site. We use this information solely for the purpose of evaluating general usage of the website, by compiling reports on website activity and related internet usage. This information may be transferred to trusted third parties, processing this information on our behalf, and who handle that information securely and confidentially, consistent with our privacy and security policies. By using this website, you consent to the processing of this web activity in the manner and for the purposes set out above. No personal information is cross referenced in these reports and the information reported is aggregate in nature.

Registration for certain services is required. In order to use free trial or to purchase services, visitors and/or members must first complete our registration form. During registration a user must give certain contact information, but we never sell or give away this information, without express permission from the user. It is only gathered to contact the user about services on our site for which s/he has expressed interest. It is required that we gather certain unique identifiers (username, password, etc.), only to permit authorized access to this site.

We require information from the user on our order form. We have an order form, and collect personal information sufficient to process credit card or eCheck orders. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and possibly financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). If we have trouble processing an order, we use the information to contact the user. This information is used for shipping and billing purposes and to complete customer orders and maintain their payment history. This information is stored for later reference for billing and subscription management.

We always use industry-standard encryption technologies. We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

Use of End-User Data. End-User Data is the consumer data we collect on your behalf, when your users access our services. This end-user data is owned by you. We never share, sell, or disclose any end-user data, unless disclosed here. We retain end-user data in the course of providing our services, and that data is destroyed after the end of your subscription period. Personally identifiable end-user information is used to process payment transactions on your behalf, communicate status of payments and related transactions, and for no other purpose.

We occasionally send email newsletters to users of our services. We publish a newsletter, and we send it out a maximum of four times per year. We never sell or share our subscribers' email addresses to anyone at anytime. All such mailings have an opt-out link, and clearly state our contact information. You may unsubscribe from these mailings at any time.

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement.

## Conflict Resolution

We are committed to resolving disputes within 24-48 hours. If problems arise, users may contact us by email or telephone. We require a written notification of complaints.

## Contact Information

If site users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us by phone at 303-395-3456 or by email.

DoJiggy Privacy Statement - updated October 2008
